tanphysics.com 2015-12-06

# Tan Physics - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) discloses how The Logic Team, Inc. uses the personal information it gathers on this site. We will notify you of changes by posting the new policy on this website. 

By using our services or submitting information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to provide our services. You can opt-out and decide not to provide the requested personal information. However, by doing so, you will not be able to purchase any products and you will not receive our email newsletters. You can also request that we no use any information you have by emailing Support@TanPhysics.com.

The personal information we collect includes your name, email address, shipping address, and payment information. Other information we collect is clearly labeled at the time of collection. Our primary use of your personal information is to process and ship your order, as well as to provide customer support. We use your payment information to obtain payment. Payment information includes your name, card number, and other information necessary to process the transaction. We use an unaffiliated, credit card processing company to process your payment. We transfer your payment information—and you authorize us to do so—to this company solely for this purpose. We use your shipping information to ship you the products you order. We use unaffiliated shipping companies to ship your product. We transfer your shipping information to the shipper solely for this purpose, and you authorize us to do so. We use your email address to send you our newsletter, promotions, and reordering information. We also use your personal information to display advertising to you and to contact you if you start an order but do not complete the process.

We automatically collect certain information from visitors to our site, such as Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and clickstream data. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve the quality of the services we provide. We do not respond to your browser’s “do not track” signals or other mechanisms for indicating your preference regarding the collection personally identifiable information. Instead, we use Google Analytics for remarketing (also known as retargeting) to advertise online. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads to you across the Internet. Google, third-party vendors, and we use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to this website. We also permit Google to track your use of our site through its AdSense program. 

We take measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. We carefully limit access to the database in which your personal information is stored. Additionally, we share and transfer your personal information only in the ways set forth in this privacy policy.

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. 

This website is directed at teenagers and adults and not to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through our website. Similarly, because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we do not condition the participation of a child under 13 in activities on providing personally identifiable information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

Contact us at the address below if you want us to change or delete any information that we have about you. We will respond to your request to access, update, or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity.

This website is owned and operated by:  
The Logic Team, Inc.  
PO Box 1084  
Old Saybrook, CT 06475

This privacy policy is effective as of March 21, 2014.
